This is uru metal. [IMG:left]
This is vibranium, so what's [IMG:right]
the difference? [IMG:wtd]
Most people think vibranium is [IMG:right]
Marvel's strongest metal. [IMG:right]
It's not. [IMG:disagree]
Uru metal. [IMG:left]
Uru is a mystical forged [IMG:left]
metal from Asgard that absorbs [IMG:left]
magic and spell enchantments, growing [IMG:left]
stronger the more energy is [IMG:left]
poured into it. [IMG:left]
But vibranium is a rare [IMG:right]
cosmic metal that absorbs kinetic [IMG:right]
physical force and vibrations converting [IMG:right]
impacts into stored kinetic energy. [IMG:right]
Vibranium stops physical attacks while [IMG:remember_this]
Uru absorbs mystical power. [IMG:remember_this]
Follow for more. [IMG:final_end]